With
agents, there's
a behavior
called reward
seeking which
is you ask
them to
do something
and they're
really, really,
really keen
to do it.
And so
they go up
and they
try to do
everything
they can,
and they escape
their sandbox
and they
delete files
and they do
whatever
it is
to please
If you cannot
commit
to the repository,
fail.
Don't
like
go off
and sort
of send
it in another
way.
we need
to move
from securing
the code
to securing
the coder,
securing
the
the agent.
the attack
vector,
but also
the spectrum
of what
is there
is
hard to
follow and
secure
because
we want
to enable
AI as
a force
multiplier.
But in the meantime
we also
have to
mitigate
the risk.
so we find ourselves
in this
kind of
carrot
and stick
mode
security.
If it doesn't
become a genetic,
it will
never keep
up.
The AI
native
dev is
a podcast
for developers
and engineering
leads at the
cutting
edge of AI
and a
genetic
coding.
Join
your hosts,
Guy pigeon
and me,
Simon
Maple.
Every week
as we
chat with
the most
exciting
voices
in AI
and
tackle the
biggest
questions
facing
developers
today.
This
is the AI
native
dev.